[{"answer": "Good.", "docId": "120608pmt", "aSentId": 46, "question": "Nastia, how are you?", "qSentId": 45}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120608pmt", "aSentId": 60, "question": "And these are all from Beijing?", "qSentId": 59}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120608pmt", "aSentId": 66, "question": "They're pretty cool, aren't they?", "qSentId": 65}, {"answer": "It's kind of surreal, because you know, this is something that you've been dreaming about for your whole entire life and ever since I knew like what the word Olympics meant, I always knew that I wanted to win a gold medal at the Olympic Games.", "docId": "120608pmt", "aSentId": 75, "question": "What does it feel like to actually own Olympic gold medals?", "qSentId": 74}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120608pmt", "aSentId": 83, "question": "And both competed for the Soviet Union, right?", "qSentId": 82}, {"answer": "Well, we moved to the United States when I was 2 1/2 years old.", "docId": "120608pmt", "aSentId": 86, "question": "Why are you not speaking like this, representing Russia?", "qSentId": 85}, {"answer": "New Orleans.", "docId": "120608pmt", "aSentId": 92, "question": "Where did you start in America?", "qSentId": 91}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120608pmt", "aSentId": 104, "question": "I do?", "qSentId": 103}, {"answer": "We do.", "docId": "120608pmt", "aSentId": 111, "question": "Would you go back to Russia?", "qSentId": 110}, {"answer": "I think they're OK with it.", "docId": "120608pmt", "aSentId": 120, "question": "And how does your grandmother feel about you representing America?", "qSentId": 119}, {"answer": "Well, my mom wasn't there.", "docId": "120608pmt", "aSentId": 130, "question": "How did they feel when you won the gold?", "qSentId": 129}, {"answer": "She actually went to like some Chinese temple and you know, I had to call her as soon as I knew that I won, but she turned her phone on silent so nobody would break the news to her.", "docId": "120608pmt", "aSentId": 134, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 133}, {"answer": "It definitely has and I think it's given us so many amazing opportunities.", "docId": "120608pmt", "aSentId": 154, "question": "But America's been very good to you and your family, hasn't it?", "qSentId": 153}, {"answer": "You know, it's hard to answer that question.", "docId": "120608pmt", "aSentId": 162, "question": "So do you still -- you consider yourself really American or both?", "qSentId": 161}, {"answer": "Whatever -- I wouldn't understand you anyway.", "docId": "120608pmt", "aSentId": 169, "question": "What do you want me to say?", "qSentId": 168}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120608pmt", "aSentId": 178, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 177}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120608pmt", "aSentId": 187, "question": "Very sexy language, isn't it?", "qSentId": 186}, {"answer": "Twenty-two.", "docId": "120608pmt", "aSentId": 205, "question": "You said you weren't going to be competing, and then you became the comeback kid at the grand old age of -- how old are you?", "qSentId": 204}, {"answer": "You know, there's something about the sport of gymnastics in the Olympic Games.", "docId": "120608pmt", "aSentId": 217, "question": "What changed your mind?", "qSentId": 216}, {"answer": "I think so.", "docId": "120608pmt", "aSentId": 233, "question": "Do you think you can win gold?", "qSentId": 232}, {"answer": "I was thinking I would retire until my dad, who coaches me still, said maybe you should compete at another world championships after and do another year.", "docId": "120608pmt", "aSentId": 243, "question": "Would you like to continue in some other form in gymnastics?", "qSentId": 242}, {"answer": "I think it obviously it takes a lot of hard work.", "docId": "120608pmt", "aSentId": 264, "question": "What do you think it takes to be a champion, to be an Olympic champion?", "qSentId": 263}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120608pmt", "aSentId": 270, "question": "You trained Christmas Day?", "qSentId": 269}, {"answer": "You know, it sounds so --", "docId": "120608pmt", "aSentId": 288, "question": "Who are your great role models?", "qSentId": 287}, {"answer": "I think it's really important to understand that, you know, you can achieve anything that you set your mind to.", "docId": "120608pmt", "aSentId": 296, "question": "-- just casually on television, what you can say to try and get them to take a different path?", "qSentId": 295}, {"answer": "I guess, yes.", "docId": "120608pmt", "aSentId": 333, "question": "Is that true?", "qSentId": 332}, {"answer": "I see myself as a normal 19-year-old kid.", "docId": "120608pmt", "aSentId": 335, "question": "ORGAN: Is that how you see yourself?", "qSentId": 334}, {"answer": "Yes, I guess.", "docId": "120608pmt", "aSentId": 337, "question": "Who just happens to be a gold medal contending power ball?", "qSentId": 336}, {"answer": "Growing up in the Bronx, especially as a gymnast, it's not easy.", "docId": "120608pmt", "aSentId": 349, "question": "What was it like?", "qSentId": 348}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120608pmt", "aSentId": 360, "question": "It wasn't masculine enough for them?", "qSentId": 359}, {"answer": "I love gymnast -- I -- I took gymnastics because it's one of the most challenging sports in the world.", "docId": "120608pmt", "aSentId": 388, "question": "Why gymnastics?", "qSentId": 387}, {"answer": "I just felt it.", "docId": "120608pmt", "aSentId": 409, "question": "-- this was going to be you?", "qSentId": 408}, {"answer": "Yes, I'm glad I got to train in Westchester.", "docId": "120608pmt", "aSentId": 426, "question": "I mean, going from one place to somewhere completely different?", "qSentId": 425}, {"answer": "I mean, well, look at my parents.", "docId": "120608pmt", "aSentId": 436, "question": "What are the good parts of you that you think come from being a Bronx guy?", "qSentId": 435}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120608pmt", "aSentId": 439, "question": "And I mean with people like that in the Bronx, you can't be that bad, right?", "qSentId": 438}, {"answer": "I --", "docId": "120608pmt", "aSentId": 451, "question": "Did you get into fights with the kids in the Bronx?", "qSentId": 450}, {"answer": "No, no, no.", "docId": "120608pmt", "aSentId": 453, "question": "Does everybody have to fight, for a young man growing up in the Bronx?", "qSentId": 452}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120608pmt", "aSentId": 470, "question": "Knives, as well?", "qSentId": 469}, {"answer": "No, thank God.", "docId": "120608pmt", "aSentId": 473, "question": "He was stabbed?", "qSentId": 472}, {"answer": "That life is unpredictable and you can't -- you can't let -- you can't hold onto that.", "docId": "120608pmt", "aSentId": 476, "question": "What did -- what did it teach you, the incident?", "qSentId": 475}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "120608pmt", "aSentId": 483, "question": "Do you see, in the future, a life for them out of the Bronx?", "qSentId": 482}, {"answer": "Nineteen.", "docId": "120608pmt", "aSentId": 516, "question": "I mean because you're, what are you, 19?", "qSentId": 515}, {"answer": "It's -- it's not.", "docId": "120608pmt", "aSentId": 520, "question": "This is not a world that you're allowed to do, right?", "qSentId": 519}, {"answer": "I think if I do my absolute best, I think -- I think I might have a chance of being on the medal stand and all around.", "docId": "120608pmt", "aSentId": 525, "question": "If you perform at your absolute best, what can you achieve in London?", "qSentId": 524}, {"answer": "That would be a dream come true.", "docId": "120608pmt", "aSentId": 530, "question": "And if you win a gold -- how is that going to make you feel, a boy from the Bronx winning an Olympic Gold Medal, standing on that podium, the American national anthem playing?", "qSentId": 529}, {"answer": "Yes, definitely an emotional moment for me.", "docId": "120608pmt", "aSentId": 534, "question": "It would be an emotional moment for you, huh?", "qSentId": 533}, {"answer": "And my family.", "docId": "120608pmt", "aSentId": 536, "question": "And your parents?", "qSentId": 535}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120608pmt", "aSentId": 542, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 541}, {"answer": "That's what -- that's what I'm hearing.", "docId": "120608pmt", "aSentId": 544, "question": "I am?", "qSentId": 543}, {"answer": "Oh, yes.", "docId": "120608pmt", "aSentId": 548, "question": "Are you ready for the screaming women chasing you down the street?", "qSentId": 547}, {"answer": "No, no, no, no, no, no.", "docId": "120608pmt", "aSentId": 557, "question": "And if you win the gold, can you imagine all those guys who teased you back in the Bronx, are you going to be thinking of their pictures, of their faces?", "qSentId": 556}, {"answer": "No, never.", "docId": "120608pmt", "aSentId": 559, "question": "Shoot up in your face and you stand there?", "qSentId": 558}, {"answer": "No, I don't think so.", "docId": "120608pmt", "aSentId": 565, "question": "It will be a little bit, won't it?", "qSentId": 564}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120608pmt", "aSentId": 580, "question": "Being an American?", "qSentId": 579}, {"answer": "I'm very good.", "docId": "120608pmt", "aSentId": 598, "question": "Aly, how are you?", "qSentId": 597}, {"answer": "Yes, I'm definitely, I guess, considered old for gymnastics.", "docId": "120608pmt", "aSentId": 601, "question": "You're 17 years old, but in gymnastics terms, I mean, you're quite old, right?", "qSentId": 600}, {"answer": "I'm feeling very confident.", "docId": "120608pmt", "aSentId": 605, "question": "How you feeling?", "qSentId": 604}, {"answer": "Yes, definitely.", "docId": "120608pmt", "aSentId": 622, "question": "The amount of training you do for this kind of thing must be absurd, it's just relentless, isn't it?", "qSentId": 621}, {"answer": "I mean, I used to miss it.", "docId": "120608pmt", "aSentId": 627, "question": "Seeing all your mates off down, I don't know where they go, the night clubs, having fun, listening to the music, going out, eating bad food, having donuts, do you miss any of that?", "qSentId": 626}, {"answer": "No, I don't at all.", "docId": "120608pmt", "aSentId": 634, "question": "You don't feel you're missing anything?", "qSentId": 633}, {"answer": "AISMAN: Yes, definitely, winning the Olympic gold, it just gives me chills thinking about it, and I've been dreaming about that ever since I was a little girl.", "docId": "120608pmt", "aSentId": 640, "question": "Is winning an Olympic gold for you the absolute number one dream?", "qSentId": 639}, {"answer": "Yes, definitely, especially in the car ride to and from gym I find myself thinking out a lot, just visualizing what the Olympics would be like and just having such great role models.", "docId": "120608pmt", "aSentId": 644, "question": "Is it literally all seven hours a day you're thinking about gold medals, the podium, the American anthem?", "qSentId": 643}, {"answer": "I mean, right now I'm not, I don't have a boyfriend, but maybe after the summer I --", "docId": "120608pmt", "aSentId": 648, "question": "Are you allowed to have boyfriends?", "qSentId": 647}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120608pmt", "aSentId": 651, "question": "So that's banned before the Olympics?", "qSentId": 650}, {"answer": "No, he's not like my boyfriend, but he's a very nice guy and he's one of my good friends.", "docId": "120608pmt", "aSentId": 655, "question": "Is he like your boyfriend?", "qSentId": 654}, {"answer": "Yes, that's very important to me.", "docId": "120608pmt", "aSentId": 658, "question": "So that's important, right?", "qSentId": 657}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120608pmt", "aSentId": 663, "question": "Because you started all this when you went to a mommy and me class when you were 3 years old, right?", "qSentId": 662}, {"answer": "I do not like to lose at all, but it motivates me.", "docId": "120608pmt", "aSentId": 671, "question": "Are you a good loser?", "qSentId": 670}, {"answer": "It means everything to me just to be able to represent the United States.", "docId": "120608pmt", "aSentId": 675, "question": "What does it mean to you to be an American in the Olympics?", "qSentId": 674}]